Welcome back to the Engine Room Records
Planetarium.
Following the fragmentation event, the
central engine has been salvaged and
transported to the Star City Orbital Ward.
Diagnostics indicate a complete and permanent
severing of the T-10 power conduit.
Automated systems below the damage threshold
have officially failed. Strict manual
maintenance protocols must now be initiated to
ensure system survival.
Strapped down to the diagnostic bed Static and
the sirens ringing in my head They towed the
broken metal to the star city dock Now I'm
running my life on a four hour clock The
automated systems are completely dead I've got
to run the heavy engine on the manual instead The
T-10 conduit is severed in the dark I lost the
lower thrusters but I still have the spark Lock
the iron, don't keep the perimeter tight I'm
learning how to fly it in the middle of the night.
Star City Orbital Ward. Strapped to the table,
strapped to the board I hate the heavy chair, I
hate the diagnostic room But I'm pushing
through the fire and I'm pushing through the
gloom I've got a crew to lift me, I've got a
spotter on the time A heavy metal mountain that I
still have to climb In the orbital ward
Every 15 minutes, I've got to shift the weight
Trying to keep the pressure off, trying to stay
straight The freight dogs pull me up the
maintenance hatch A synchronized lift, a heavy
metal catch My hands are on the console, I've got
the upper gear We're rewriting the protocols
right out here The T-10 conduit is severed in the
dark I lost the lower thrusters, but I still have
the spark Lock the iron, don't keep the
perimeter tight I'm learning how to fly it in the
middle of the night! STAR CITY ORBITAL WAR!
Strapped to the table, strapped to the board I
hate the heavy chair, I hate the diagnostic room
But I'm pushing through the fire and I'm pushing
through the gloom I've got a crew to lift me, I've
got a spotter on the time The heavy metal
mountain that I still have to climb in the
orbital ward
The connection is broken.
But the hands still work.
The legs are silent.
But the engine still roars! Star City Orbit
Award! Strapped to the table, strapped to the
board I hate the heavy chair, I hate the
diagnostic room But I'm pushing through the
fire and I'm pushing through the gloom I've got a
crew to lift me, I've got a spotter on the time A
heavy metal mountain that I still have to climb
in the orbital ward
Shift the weight.
Watch the clock. Star City Dark.